<row Id="208433" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="208446" CreationDate="2008-10-16T12:57:34.090" Score="74" ViewCount="25804" Body="&lt;p&gt;Very basic question: how do I write a &lt;code&gt;short&lt;/code&gt; literal in C++?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;2&lt;/code&gt; is an &lt;code&gt;int&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;2U&lt;/code&gt; is an &lt;code&gt;unsigned int&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;2L&lt;/code&gt; is a &lt;code&gt;long&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;2LL&lt;/code&gt; is a &lt;code&gt;long long&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;2.0f&lt;/code&gt; is a &lt;code&gt;float&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;2.0&lt;/code&gt; is a &lt;code&gt;double&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;'\2'&lt;/code&gt; is a &lt;code&gt;char&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But how would I write a &lt;code&gt;short&lt;/code&gt; literal?  I tried &lt;code&gt;2S&lt;/code&gt; but that gives a compiler warning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="18511" OwnerDisplayName="Kip" LastEditorUserId="18511" LastEditorDisplayName="Kip" LastEditDate="2015-04-22T21:39:49.070" LastActivityDate="2016-06-08T16:20:57.147" Title="How do I write a short literal in C++?" Tags="&lt;c++&gt;&lt;literals&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="9" />
<row Id="208510" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="208492" CreationDate="2008-10-16T13:19:00.943" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'd go with a WCF REST-based service, because you'll be able to transmit pure data without the overhead of the SOAP header (and other envelope nonsense) that comes with the SOAP-based classic .asmx web service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22303" OwnerDisplayName="fallen888" LastActivityDate="2008-10-16T13:19:00.943" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="208524" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="208484" CreationDate="2008-10-16T13:21:50.407" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Code version management and database version management are two very different problems. The solution that  I prefer is done in three stages (Test, Deployment Test, Live) rather than two.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Update the code and apply database changes via scripts in the development environment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Download the live database to a deployment test environment, restore it and apply the change scripts&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Test the code against the 'synchronised' live database&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Update the live environment via svn from the relevant branch on the repository (we do it via ssh tunneling since it's a linux environment) and apply the change scripts to the live db&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Edit:&lt;/b&gt; The update for the live environment is best done using export rather than checkout/update. This doesn't leave svn's control file hanging around. This may or may not have security implications, it does force you to specify which branch you're checking out each time though.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your 'one click' could probably be scripted for the last step.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="28158" OwnerDisplayName="Bell" LastEditorUserId="28158" LastEditorDisplayName="Bell" LastEditDate="2008-10-16T13:27:15.887" LastActivityDate="2008-10-16T13:27:15.887" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="208745" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="208659" CreationDate="2008-10-16T14:14:52.840" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, since logical expression are just a subset of mathematical expression, you may want to try &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.codeplex.com/ncalc&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;NCalc - Mathematical Expressions Evaluator for .NET&lt;/a&gt; over on CodePlex.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="12725" OwnerDisplayName="James Curran" LastActivityDate="2008-10-16T14:14:52.840" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="203358" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2009-10-15T00:44:56.847" Score="5" ViewCount="2239" Body="&lt;p&gt;I want to set a style on the first and last TabItems in a TabControl, and have them updated as the visibility of the TabItems is changed.  I can't see a way to do so with triggers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What we're after looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;| &gt; &gt; &gt; |&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the visibility of TabItems are determined by binding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do have it working in code.  On TabItem visibility changed, enumerate through TabItems until you find the first visible one.  Set the style on that one.  For all other visible TabItems, set them to the pointy style (so that the previously first visible one is now pointy).  Then start from the end until you find a visible TabItem and set the last style on that one.  (This also lets us address an issue with TabControl where it will display the content of a non-visible TabItem if none of the visible TabItems are selected.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There's undoubtably improvements I could make to my method, but I'm not convinced that it IS the right approach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How would you approach this?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="28074" LastEditorUserId="66708" LastEditorDisplayName="Jexia" LastEditDate="2010-10-15T00:37:22.290" LastActivityDate="2013-02-06T17:45:43.123" Title="Setting style on first and last visible TabItem of TabControl" Tags="&lt;.net&gt;&lt;wpf&gt;&lt;xaml&gt;&lt;tabcontrol&gt;&lt;tabitem&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
<row Id="204202" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="204211" CreationDate="2008-10-15T09:55:58.573" Score="12" ViewCount="25302" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would like to know exactly how the &quot;Is&quot; command works in Linux and Unix.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As far as I know, ls forks &amp;amp; exec to the linux/unix shell and then gets the output (of the current file tree. eg./home/ankit/).  I need a more detailed explanation, as I am not sure about what happens after calling fork.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Could any one please explain the functionality of the 'ls' command in detail?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="24813" OwnerDisplayName="Ankit S" LastEditorUserId="672" LastEditorDisplayName="kogus" LastEditDate="2008-10-28T20:58:09.303" LastActivityDate="2013-05-14T02:23:29.077" Title="How does the 'ls' command work in Linux/Unix?" Tags="&lt;linux&gt;&lt;unix&gt;&lt;open-source&gt;&lt;operating-system&gt;&lt;solaris&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="9" />